[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What was your feeling today as you sat in the courtroom watching the events?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "It was definitely very sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "When you saw the shooter up close, as you did today, did it shock you even more that he was able to arm himself in the horrifying manner that he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Why do you want to deport me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, we did it as a way to bring attention to the fact that we have all of these foreigners and the Russian government, the official Chinese government, now said political power goes out the barrel of a gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Are you finished?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Yes, I am finished.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["70 percent"]}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "JJ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "There were about 11,458, and about 70 percent of those were gang related.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 143, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain last year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "How many great white sharks --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "kill people every year but they're scared to swim?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "A very low amount.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "How many, do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "That was only a few hundred.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "How many gun murders?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "I actually -- actually brought statistics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Why don't you go back and face the charges with the hacking scandal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Answer this question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":"], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Why did you get fired from \"The Daily Mirror\" for putting that fag stories?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "How --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "You know the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Do you understand the difference in 11,000 and 35?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Yes, England wants to ban knives now because tens of thousands are getting stabbed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Do you understand the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Do you understand --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "-- and 11,000?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "They know your script.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", "-NONE-", "-NONE-", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Let me ask you one question, which weapon was predominantly used in the Aurora movie theater shooting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NN", ",", "WDT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "ONES: An M-4 AR-15 variant.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Now I believe that there were others --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Do you know which weapon was used in the Oregon shopping mall mass shooting recently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WDT", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "I understand that people who were mentally ill on all the --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oregon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Do you know what the weapon used was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Listen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Do you have a body guard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Alex.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Why do you have body guards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I don't have a body guard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dianne Feinstein"]}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Let me ask you this question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Why does Dianne Feinstein --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", ":", "NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "-- to try and take Mr. And Mrs. America's guns?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Don't be (INAUDIBLE) over me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. And Mrs. America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "What was the weapon used at Sandy Hook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I have already gone over that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What was the weapon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "It's a 223 M-4.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Why is the government (INAUDIBLE) against this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Why -- Alex. I don't --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "What about \"Fast and Furious\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "``", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Alex.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Why did our government ship guns to Mexico?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Calm down.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mexico"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "To blame the Second Amendment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Let's have a debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 390, "question": "A false flag?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Alex, I get accused --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 392, "question": "To blame the Second Amendment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I get accused --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex."]}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Why they blow up buildings down the street here in New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Alex. Alex. I get accused when I get you guys on of talking over you, of being rude.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "All right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Alex, why do people need them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Go commit suicide by killing a bunch of kids and here's the gun to use --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Why do people need them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "They need them to protect us from the number one killer in history.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "-- therefore have an AR-15 if they want one?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Statistically, where there's mo more guns, there's lower crime.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Is they're half your sponsors?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Stick to the topic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Who do you believe was behind 9/11?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "I absolutely know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Yes, but who do you believe was behind it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I have the proof.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS Radio"]}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Who, Alex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "They announced they blew up the towers on CBS Radio.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", ":", "NNP", ":", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 530, "question": "The American government?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Criminal elements of the military and industrial complex, the same ones that staged (INAUDIBLE), the same ones that staged operation --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Alex. Alex. Do you mean that President Bush and his administration were behind 9/11?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I mean that even mainstream news reported that the hijackers were ordered to be allowed into the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "But is that what you believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "The government -- Hitler fired bombs and turned rash tag, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "How many guns do you own?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I probably own more than 50 firearms.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "What is brave about wanting to stop 20 more children getting murders?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "I don't think you're right about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "ERSHOWITZ: Because we think it's their issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "How are you doing, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Explain to me why you believe that the answer to these gun massacres is to have a lot more guns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Why are on Earth do you think these patrolmen, as you put it, who you have taken of the streets and given a bit of training to, could do any better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "We don't pick them off the streets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "What about this old quaint idea, what about taking guns off the streets rather than flooding the streets with more guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "What did you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "It was disheartening, I think, you know, I think just to see the anger there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBD", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 825, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 826, "answer": "During the aftermath of Obamacare, when there were -- the president was being held in effigy and these kinds of threatening comments of people like the man you just had on were blocking members of Congress from being able to go and vote, you may recall, of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "RB", "IN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 863, "question": "Are you surprised that following the assassinations of John F. Kennedy and of Bobby Kennedy that we are in a position in America now where these kind of lawless mass shootings are happening with regularity and no one is doing much about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 864, "answer": "ENNEDY: Well, as I said, I think that the lack of discourse -- so that that is really what's offensive in our country, where we should be able to debate our problems without impugning the integrity of the people who have positions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John F. Kennedy", "Bobby Kennedy"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}]